[
    {
        "PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING",
        "SYSTEM":"HIGH PERFORMANCE ER COLLET CHUCK WITH POWER NUT",
        "TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A",
        "PART NUMBER":"H100-16ERP406",
        "STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-16ERP406.stp",
        "2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-16ERP406.dxf",
        "PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-16ERP406.pdf"
    },
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"HIGH PERFORMANCE ER COLLET CHUCK WITH POWER NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-16ERP642","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-16ERP642.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-16ERP642.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-16ERP642.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"HIGH PERFORMANCE ER COLLET CHUCK WITH POWER NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-20ERP406","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-20ERP406.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-20ERP406.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-20ERP406.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"HIGH PERFORMANCE ER COLLET CHUCK WITH POWER NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-20ERP642","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-20ERP642.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-20ERP642.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-20ERP642.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"HIGH PERFORMANCE ER COLLET CHUCK WITH POWER NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-25ERP406","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-25ERP406.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-25ERP406.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-25ERP406.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"HIGH PERFORMANCE ER COLLET CHUCK WITH POWER NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-32ERP406","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-32ERP406.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-32ERP406.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-32ERP406.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"HIGH PERFORMANCE ER COLLET CHUCK WITH POWER NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-32ERP642","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-32ERP642.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-32ERP642.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-32ERP642.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"HIGH PERFORMANCE ER COLLET CHUCK WITH POWER NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-40ERP406","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-40ERP406.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-40ERP406.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-40ERP406.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"HIGH PERFORMANCE ER COLLET CHUCK WITH POWER NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-40ERP484","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-40ERP484.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-40ERP484.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-40ERP484.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"PERFORMANCE ER COLLET CHUCK WITH COOLANT NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-16ERC416","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-16ERC416.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-16ERC416.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-16ERC416.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"PERFORMANCE ER COLLET CHUCK WITH COOLANT NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-16ERC652","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-16ERC652.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-16ERC652.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-16ERC652.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"PERFORMANCE ER COLLET CHUCK WITH COOLANT NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-20ERC416","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-20ERC416.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-20ERC416.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-20ERC416.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"PERFORMANCE ER COLLET CHUCK WITH COOLANT NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-20ERC652","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-20ERC652.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-20ERC652.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-20ERC652.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"PERFORMANCE ER COLLET CHUCK WITH COOLANT NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-25ERC416","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-25ERC416.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-25ERC416.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-25ERC416.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"PERFORMANCE ER COLLET CHUCK WITH COOLANT NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-32ERC416","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-32ERC416.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-32ERC416.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-32ERC416.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"PERFORMANCE ER COLLET CHUCK WITH COOLANT NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-32ERC652","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-32ERC652.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-32ERC652.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-32ERC652.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"PERFORMANCE ER COLLET CHUCK WITH COOLANT NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-40ERC416","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-40ERC416.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-40ERC416.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-40ERC416.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"PERFORMANCE ER COLLET CHUCK WITH COOLANT NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-40ERC494","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-40ERC494.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-40ERC494.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-40ERC494.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"PRODUCTION ER COLLET CHUCK WITH FLUSH NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-16ERF394","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-16ERF394.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-16ERF394.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-16ERF394.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"PRODUCTION ER COLLET CHUCK WITH FLUSH NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-16ERF630","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-16ERF630.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-16ERF630.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-16ERF630.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"PRODUCTION ER COLLET CHUCK WITH FLUSH NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-20ERF394","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-20ERF394.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-20ERF394.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-20ERF394.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"PRODUCTION ER COLLET CHUCK WITH FLUSH NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-20ERF630","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-20ERF630.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-20ERF630.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-20ERF630.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"PRODUCTION ER COLLET CHUCK WITH FLUSH NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-25ERF394","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-25ERF394.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-25ERF394.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-25ERF394.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"PRODUCTION ER COLLET CHUCK WITH FLUSH NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-32ERF394","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-32ERF394.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-32ERF394.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-32ERF394.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"PRODUCTION ER COLLET CHUCK WITH FLUSH NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-32ERF630","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-32ERF630.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-32ERF630.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-32ERF630.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"PRODUCTION ER COLLET CHUCK WITH FLUSH NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-40ERF394","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-40ERF394.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-40ERF394.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-40ERF394.pdf"},
    {"PARLEC PRODUCT SOLUTION":"TOOLHOLDING","SYSTEM":"PRODUCTION ER COLLET CHUCK WITH FLUSH NUT","TAPER TYPE":"HSK 100 FORM A","PART NUMBER":"H100-40ERF472","STP FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\3D (.STP)\\H100-40ERF472.stp","2D CAD DXF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.DXF)\\H100-40ERF472.dxf","PDF FILE":"V:\\CUSTOMER FILES\\HSK 100A\\2D (.PDF)\\H100-40ERF472.pdf"}
]
